https://sobi-northamerica.com/site-privacy-policy

General
Sobi, Inc. respects the privacy of every individual who visits http://www.sobi-northamerica.com (the "Web Site"). This Privacy Policy outlines the information Sobi, Inc. will collect and how we will use that information.
Personally Identifiable Information
There may be cases where Sobi, Inc. will ask you for personally-identifiable information such as your name, mailing address, and email address. For example, we may request personally-identifiable information when you participate in a survey, contest, or other service that requires registration or subscription. Sobi, Inc. will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily.
When you view the website, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file and will help us to offer increased personalization and functionality. With most internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
Except as stated in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise stated at the time personally-identifiable information is gathered, we will not provide personally-identifiable information to third parties who are not under the direction and control of Sobi, Inc..
Children
The Web Site is not directed at individuals under thirteen years of age, and Sobi, Inc. does not intend to collect any personally-identifiable information from such individuals, unless otherwise stated at the time such information is collected.
Information Collected Automatically
Sobi, Inc. may also automatically collect non-personally-identifiable information about your use of the Web Site, such as the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account), the date and time you access the Web Site, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Web Site. This information will not be linked to personally-identifiable information. Sobi, Inc. may use this information to analyze and enhance the Web Site, and may aggregate this information and share such aggregated information with business partners, sponsors and other third parties.
Links to Other Web Sites
The Web Site may allow links to various other web sites. Sobi, Inc. assumes no responsibility for the information practices of sites you are able to access through the Web Site. These links to other sites do not imply affiliation or endorsement of a linked site.
Security
The importance of security for all personally-identifiable information associated with visitors to the Web Site is of utmost concern to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, Sobi, Inc. cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your personally-identifiable information, we will take reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.
Your Acceptance of These Terms
By using the Web Site, you signify your assent to the Sobi, Inc. Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use the Web Site. Your continued use of the Web Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Sobi, Inc. will, however, use personally-identifiable information only in accordance with the version of the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.
Terms and Conditions of Use
Use of the Web Site is governed by the Sobi, Inc. Legal Statement.
Site Privacy Policy
General
Sobi, Inc. respects the privacy of every individual who visits http://www.sobi-northamerica.com (the "Web Site"). This Privacy Policy outlines the information Sobi, Inc. will collect and how we will use that information.
Personally Identifiable Information
There may be cases where Sobi, Inc. will ask you for personally-identifiable information such as your name, mailing address, and email address. For example, we may request personally-identifiable information when you participate in a survey, contest, or other service that requires registration or subscription. Sobi, Inc. will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily.
When you view the website, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file and will help us to offer increased personalization and functionality. With most internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
Except as stated in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise stated at the time personally-identifiable information is gathered, we will not provide personally-identifiable information to third parties who are not under the direction and control of Sobi, Inc..
Children
The Web Site is not directed at individuals under thirteen years of age, and Sobi, Inc. does not intend to collect any personally-identifiable information from such individuals, unless otherwise stated at the time such information is collected.
Information Collected Automatically
Sobi, Inc. may also automatically collect non-personally-identifiable information about your use of the Web Site, such as the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account), the date and time you access the Web Site, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our Web Site. This information will not be linked to personally-identifiable information. Sobi, Inc. may use this information to analyze and enhance the Web Site, and may aggregate this information and share such aggregated information with business partners, sponsors and other third parties.
Links to Other Web Sites
The Web Site may allow links to various other web sites. Sobi, Inc. assumes no responsibility for the information practices of sites you are able to access through the Web Site. These links to other sites do not imply affiliation or endorsement of a linked site.
Security
The importance of security for all personally-identifiable information associated with visitors to the Web Site is of utmost concern to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, Sobi, Inc. cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your personally-identifiable information, we will take reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.
Your Acceptance of These Terms
By using the Web Site, you signify your assent to the Sobi, Inc. Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use the Web Site. Your continued use of the Web Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Sobi, Inc. will, however, use personally-identifiable information only in accordance with the version of the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.
Terms and Conditions of Use
Use of the Web Site is governed by the Sobi, Inc. Legal Statement.
